mpob.gov.my 2014-06-28

# The Official Portal Of Malaysian Palm Oil Board

This page explains our privacy policy which includes the use and protection of any information submitted by visitors.

 **Information Collected**

No personally identifiable information is gathered during the browsing of the Portal except for information given by you via e-mails.

 **Cookies**

Certain websites generate ‘cookies’, which are collected by web-servers to enable them to recognise your future visits. These cookies do not permanently record data and they are not stored on your computer’s hard drive. Once you close your browser, the cookie is deleted.

 **Links to Other Sites/Portals**

The Portal contains links to other websites/portals, both Government and Non-Government organisations. This privacy policy applies only to our site and you should be aware that other sites/portals linked by the Portal may have different privacy policies and we highly recommend that you read and understand the privacy statements of each site.

 **Changes to this Policy**

If this privacy policy changes in any way, it will be updated on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures you are updated on the information which is collected, how it is used and under what circumstances, if any, it is shared with other parties. 

### Daily CPO Prices

### Visitors

**Visitor :  
  
since May 1,2000**

Best Viewed In **1024 x 768** pixel resolutions and above, and compatible with the following browsers:  
| You may need the followings to view certain areas of the portal:  
---|---
